http://www.kingbabystudio.com/pages/terms-privacy

Skip to Content
15% OFF ORDERS OF $500 OR MORE AND FREE SHIPPING ON ANY USA ORDER OF $50 OR MORE!
My shopping cart
Your cart is currently empty.
***GIVEAWAY ALERT***
Sign up to our email list for a chance to win! We’re giving away 5 of our special edition King Baby X Carhartt vests.Winners will be contacted next week - Good Luck!!
Join our mailing list
Home
Terms & Privacy
Terms of Use
Effective Date: 05/31/2014
These Terms of Use apply to www.KingBabyStudio.com (the "Site”). The Site is operated by King Baby Inc, ("King Baby”). Throughout the Site, the terms "we,” "us” and "our” refer to King Baby. King Baby offers the Site, including all information, tools and services available from the Site, to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all the terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here. Your use of the Site constitutes your agreement to these Terms of Use.
Accuracy, Completeness and Timeliness of Information on the Site
King Baby is not responsible if information made available on the Site is not accurate, complete or current. The material on the Site is provided for general information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. Any reliance on the material on the Site is at your own risk. The Site may contain certain historical information. Historical information necessarily is not current and is provided for your reference only. We reserve the right to modify the contents of the Site at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on the Site. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to the Site.
Use of Materials on the Site
All content on the Site (including, without limitation, text, design, graphics, logos, icons, images, audio clips, downloads, interfaces, code and software, as well as the selection and arrangement thereof) is the exclusive property of and owned by King Baby, its licensors or its content providers and is protected by copyright, trademark and other applicable laws. You may access, copy, download and print the material contained on the Site for your personal and non-commercial use, provided you do not modify or delete any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notice that appears on the material you access, copy, download or print. Any other use of content on the Site, including but not limited to the modification, distribution, transmission, performance, broadcast, publication, uploading, licensing, reverse engineering, transfer or sale of, or the creation of derivative works from, any material, information, software, products or services obtained from the Site, or use of the Site for purposes competitive to King Baby, is expressly prohibited. You agree to abide by all additional restrictions displayed on the Site as it may be updated from time to time. King Baby reserves the right to refuse or cancel any person’s registration for the Site, remove any person from the Site or prohibit any person from using the Site for any reason whatsoever. King Baby, or its licensors or content providers, retain full and complete title to the material provided on the Site, including all associated intellectual property rights, and provide this material to you under a license that is revocable at any time in King Baby’s sole discretion. King Baby neither warrants nor represents that your use of materials on the Site will not infringe rights of third parties not affiliated with King Baby.
You may not use contact information provided on the Site for unauthorized purposes, including marketing. You may not use any hardware or software intended to damage or interfere with the proper working of the Site or to surreptitiously intercept any system, data or personal information from the Site. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the Site in any way. King Baby reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to limit or terminate your access to or use of the Site at any time without notice. Termination of your access or use will not waive or affect any other right or relief to which King Baby may be entitled at law or in equity.
Materials You Submit
You acknowledge that you are responsible for any material you may submit via the Site, including the legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality and copyright of any such material. You may not upload to, distribute or otherwise publish through the Site any content that (i) is confidential, proprietary, false, fraudulent, libelous, defamatory, obscene, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, infringing on intellectual property rights, abusive, illegal or otherwise objectionable; (ii) may constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party or otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law; or (iii) may contain software viruses, political campaigning, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam.” You may not use a false email address or other identifying information, impersonate any person or entity or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any content. You may not upload commercial content onto the Site. If you do submit material, and unless we indicate otherwise, you grant King Baby an unrestricted, nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute and display such material throughout the world in any media. You further agree that King Baby is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how that you or individuals acting on your behalf provide to King Baby. You grant King Baby the right to use the name you submit in connection with such material, if the company so chooses. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all the rights to the content you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate any provision herein and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify King Baby for all claims resulting from content you supply.
Conduct on the Site
Some features that may be available on the Site require registration. By registering at and in consideration of your use of the Site you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself.
Some features on the Site require use of a password. You are responsible for protecting your password. You agree that you will be responsible for any and all statements made, and acts or omissions that occur, through the use of your password. If you have any reason to believe or become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, notify King Baby immediately. King Baby may assume that any communications the company receives under your password have been made by you unless the company receives notice otherwise. You or third parties acting on your behalf are not allowed to frame the Site or use our proprietary marks as meta tags, without our written consent. These marks include, but are not limited to, King Baby®. You may not use frames or utilize framing techniques or technology to enclose any content included on the Site without King Baby’s express written consent. Further, you may not utilize any Site content in any meta tags or any other "hidden text” techniques or technologies without King Baby’s express written consent.
You are hereby informed that King Baby has adopted and reasonably implemented a policy that provides for the termination in appropriate circumstances of subscribers and account holders of King Baby’s system or network who are repeat copyright infringers. If you believe your copyright or the copyright of a person on whose behalf you are authorized to act has been infringed, you may notify our copyright agent:
King Baby Studio Inc Legal Department 615 9th Avenue South Nashville, TN 37203 Email: legal@KingBabyStudio.com
To be effective, your notification must (i) be in writing, (ii) be provided to our copyright agent, and (iii) include substantially the following:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;
Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted;
A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
King Baby is under no obligation to post, forward, transmit, distribute or otherwise provide any material available on the Site, including material you provide to us, and so we have an absolute right to remove any material from the Site in our sole discretion at any time.
DISCLAIMERS
YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OR TERMINATE YOUR ACCESS TO THE SITE OR ANY FEATURE OR PART THEREOF AT ANY TIME. KING BABY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ANY WARRANTIES THAT MATERIALS ON THE SITE ARE NONINFRINGING, AS WELL AS WARRANTIES IMPLIED FROM A COURSE OF PERFORMANCE OR COURSE OF DEALING; THAT ACCESS TO THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; THAT THE SITE WILL BE SECURE; THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SITE AVAILABLE WILL BE VIRUS-FREE; OR THAT INFORMATION ON THE SITE WILL BE COMPLETE, ACCURATE OR TIMELY. IF YOU DOWNLOAD ANY MATERIALS FROM THE SITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIALS.  IN THE EVENT A KING BABY PRODUCT IS LISTED AT AN INCORRECT PRICE DUE TO TYPOGRAPHICAL ERROR OR SYSTEMS ERROR, KING BABY SHALL HAVE THE RIGHT TO REFUSE OR CANCEL ANY ORDERS PLACED FOR PRODUCT LISTED AT THE INCORRECT PRICE. KING BABY SHALL HAVE THE RIGHT TO REFUSE OR CANCEL ANY SUCH ORDERS WHETHER OR NOT THE ORDER HAS BEEN CONFIRMED AND YOUR CREDIT CARD CHARGED. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM KING BABYOR THROUGH OR FROM THE SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.THE COMPANY DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE SITE OR THE USE OF THE MATERIALS ON THE SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE.> IN CERTAIN JURISDICTIONS, THE LAW MAY NOT PERMIT THE DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE DISCLAIMER MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ASSUME FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY INFORMATION YOU SEND OR RECEIVE DURING YOUR USE OF THE SITE MAY NOT BE SECURE AND MAY BE INTERCEPTED BY UNAUTHORIZED PARTIES. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK AND THAT THE SITE IS MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU AT NO CHARGE. RECOGNIZING SUCH, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER KING BABYNOR ITS SUPPLIERS OR THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO THE SITE, OR ANY OTHER SITES YOU ACCESS THROUGH A LINK FROM THE SITE OR FROM ANY ACTIONS WE TAKE OR FAIL TO TAKE AS A RESULT OF COMMUNICATIONS YOU SEND TO US, OR THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES ADVERTISED IN OR OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE, KING BABY’S REMOVAL OR DELETION OF ANY MATERIALS SUBMITTED OR POSTED ON ITS SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF KING BABYOR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. THIS DISCLAIMER APPLIES, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY ARISING FROM ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECTS, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUSES, FILE CORRUPTION, COMMUNICATION-LINE FAILURE, NETWORK OR SYSTEM OUTAGE, YOUR LOSS OF PROFITS, OR THEFT, DESTRUCTION, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, LOSS OR USE OF ANY RECORD OR DATA, AND ANY OTHER TANGIBLE OR INTANGIBLE LOSS. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT NEITHER KING BABYNOR ITS SUPPLIERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY USER OF THE SITE. YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY FOR ANY OF THE ABOVE CLAIMS OR ANY DISPUTE WITH KING BABYIS TO DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THE SITE. YOU AND KING BABYAGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE SITE MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES OR THE CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED. BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, ALL OR A PORTION OF THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless King Baby and its officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, service providers, subcontractors and suppliers from and against any and all losses, liabilities, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees and court costs, arising or resulting from your use of the Site and any violation of these Terms of Use. If you cause a technical disruption of the Site or the systems transmitting the Site to you or others, you agree to be responsible for any and all losses, liabilities, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees and court costs, arising or resulting from that disruption. King Baby reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you and, in such case, you agree to cooperate with King Baby in the defense of such matter.
Jurisdiction and Applicable Law
The laws of the state of California govern these Terms of Use and your use of the Site, and you irrevocably consent to the jurisdiction of the courts located in the state of New York for any action arising out of or relating to these Terms of Use. We recognize that it is possible for you to obtain access to the Site from any jurisdiction in the world, but we have no practical ability to prevent such access. The Site has been designed to comply with the laws of the state of California and of the United States. If any material on the Site, or your use of the Site, is contrary to the laws of the place where you are when you access it, the Site is not intended for you, and we ask you not to use the Site. You are responsible for informing yourself of the laws of your jurisdiction and complying with them.
Changes to These Terms of Use
King Baby reserves the right in its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of these Terms of Use, in whole or in part, at any time, by posting revised terms on the Site. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes we make to the Terms of Use. Revised terms will take effect five days after their publication on the Site and will apply only on a going forward basis. Your continued use of the Site after that point signifies that you accept the changes.
Entire Agreement and Admissibility
This agreement and any policies or operating rules posted on the Site constitute the entire agreement and understanding between you and King Baby with respect to the subject matter thereof and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether oral or written, between the parties with respect to such subject matter. A printed version of these Terms of Use shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based on or relating to use of the Site to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.
Severability
If any provision of this agreement is unlawful, void or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of the agreement will remain in place.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about these Terms of Use or the Site, please contact us by e-mail at customerservice@KingBabyStudio.com. You also may write to us at: King Baby Studio Inc, 615 9th Avenue South Nashville, TN 37203 Thank you for visiting our Site.
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: 05/31/2014
We at King Baby Studio Inc, ("King Baby”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Online Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect at www.KingBabyStudio.com (the "Site”), how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices available to users of our Site regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices. Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:
Information We Collect
Information We Collect By Automated Means
How We Use the Information We Collect
Information We Share
Notice to California Residents
Your Rights and Choices
Data Transfers
How We Protect Personal Information
Links To Other Websites
Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
How To Contact Us
Information We Collect
The types of personal information users of our Site may submit include:
Contact information (such as name, postal address, telephone number and email address);
login credentials for the Site;
payment information (such as payment card details);
purchase and transaction information (including serial numbers for timepiece registration); and
other personal information found in content that users provide, such as through our live chat function.
Information We Collect By Automated Means
When you use our Site, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, web beacons and JavaScript. Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your device. Our Site may use cookies (such as HTTP cookies) and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plug-in-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site or other websites and online services.
In conjunction with gathering information through cookies, our web servers may log information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The web server logs also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to our Site and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. They also may log information about your interaction with the Site, such as which pages you visit. To control which web servers collect information by automated means, we may place tags on our web pages called "web beacons,” which are small files that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies. We also may send instructions to your device using JavaScript or other computer languages to gather the sorts of information described above and other details about your interactions with the Site.
We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site, such as those of Google Analytics, Adobe Omniture and Channel Intelligence. These service providers help us analyze how users use the Site. The information collected for this purpose (including your IP address or other information collected by automated means) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers. To learn more about opting out of these providers’ activities, click the relevant link below: Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be "tracked" online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast.
The Information we collect was lasted updated on December 31, 2013.
Google Analytics
Adobe Omniture
Channel Intelligence
How We Use the Information We Collect
We may use the information described above to:
Provide products and services;
create and manage your account;
process your payment;
send you catalogs and other promotional materials;
communicate with you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, offers, surveys and market research;
respond to your inquiries;
perform data analyses (including anonymization and aggregation of personal information);
operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications; analyzing our products and services; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities; and
comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.
We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection. In addition, we use information collected through automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to our Site, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse our Site, and (iii) managing our Site and other aspects of our business. We also may use this information to provide you with ads about our products when you browse this and other websites. Our Site is not designed to respond to "do not track” requests from browsers.
Information We Share
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect about you.
In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government entities, and (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).
Links To Other Websites
Our Site may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from us. Linked sites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we h3ly suggest you review. To the extent any linked websites are not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for the websites’ content, any use of the websites, or the privacy practices of the websites.
Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
This Online Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a prominent notice on our Site to notify you of any significant changes to our Online Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Online Privacy Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by email at customerservice@KingBabyStudio.com.You also may write to: Customer Service King Baby Studio Inc, 615 9th Avenue South Nashville, TN 37203
CARE AND REPAIR
Caring For Your King Baby Jewelry
Any piece of jewelry will retain its beauty and last longer if properly cared for.
Sometimes, simply cleaning a piece of jewelry can make it look like new. Ideally, jewelry should be professionally cleaned once a year. Your nearest King Baby boutique can facilitate this, or you may call 615 248-4318.
Periodic inspection and maintenance of jewelry helps prevent costly repairs or replacements. Look for loose or chipped stones, worn links, bent prongs, or malfunctioning clasps. If a problem is found, the piece should be brought in immediately for repair to prevent more extensive damage or loss.
King Baby jewelry should only be repaired at our authorized repair centers. Our facilities are designed exclusively for King Baby jewelry, and highly experienced professional jewelers will handle each repair. To find out how to deliver your piece for repair, please call 615 248-4318.
It is our experience that a jeweler unfamiliar with King Baby jewelry can do more harm than good. We will repair any piece of King Baby jewelry, but poor craftsmanship by an unauthorized jeweler is considered damage and may add to the cost of the repair.
How to Avoid Damaging Gemstones
Some gemstones are by nature more fragile than others. In general, you can prevent many problems by not exposing gemstones to chemicals such as chlorine or extreme heat or light, all of which can cause fractures, breakage, and discoloration. Salt water should be avoided, as well.
All gemstones, including diamonds, can chip, scratch, or abrade under the right circumstances. Avoid wearing rings or bracelets while doing any manual labor, including housework. Jewelry should be taken off before strenuous activity or during times when it might be subjected to sharp blows or excessive friction.
Never remove rings by pulling on the stone; the prongs or bezel can be damaged causing the stone to loosen or fall out.
Store each piece of gemstone jewelry separately in its storage pouch to prevent excessive tarnishing and scratching.
How to Clean Your King Baby Jewelry
Over time, lotions, powders, soaps, and natural skin oils can make jewelry and gemstones appear dull. Below are some tips for keeping your pieces clean and shiny.
Cleaning Silver Jewelry
Sterling silver tarnishes in the presence of common everyday items that contain sulfur, such as leather, rubber, and chlorine. Other elements to be mindful of are air pollutants and salt water. Because these substances cannot be completely avoided, it is recommended that sterling silver be routinely wiped down with the white side of the King Baby polishing cloth that came with your piece. Regular wear of your King Baby sterling silver can also help prevent tarnishing—we recommend that you enjoy and wear your King Baby jewelry every day. When not in use, store your jewelry in the pouch that came with it.
To remove heavier tarnish, wash your silver jewelry with warm water and mild soap or Connoisseurs® Jewelry Wipes. Never use anything but a clean, nub-free cotton or flannel cloth, a special sterling silver cleaning cloth, or a very soft bristle brush like a baby’s toothbrush. We do not recommend wet silver polish or dip style cleaning solutions, which will remove the antique oxidation that we intentionally apply to many King Baby silver pieces to give them their distinctive look. If more thorough cleaning is required, an authorized jeweler can clean your pieces to restore them to their original condition. We recommend having your jewelry professionally cleaned once a year.
Cleaning Gold Jewelry
Using gentle dish soap, prepare a small bowl of warm suds and soak each piece before brushing with a soft baby’s toothbrush. When clean, transfer jewelry to a strainer, rinse under warm running water, and pat dry with a soft, lint-free cloth.
Cleaning Jewelry with Crystalline Gemstones
Crystalline gemstones, such as amethyst, blue topaz, citrine, or peridot attract oils and lotions causing them to appear dull. To clean, soak them in a bowl of water with a touch of gentle dish soap. A soft baby’s toothbrush may be used to scrub around and behind the stone. After cleaning, place your jewelry in a strainer and rinse before thoroughly drying with a lint-free cloth.
Cleaning Jewelry with Organic and Opaque Gemstones
Never use an ultrasonic cleaner or chemicals (including bleach or ammonia) on organic gems and opaque stones such as pearls, opals, coral, turquoise, and lapis lazuli. They should only be wiped clean with a damp cloth. In addition, avoid contact with hairspray, lotions, and perfumes, which can be absorbed over time, causing discoloration. Opals and pearls require humidity. When storing them, make sure the environment is not too dry or they may crack.
PERSONAL SHOPPING
A King Baby Personal Shopper can take care of all your shopping needs and answer any questions you may have. As a complimentary service, our knowledgeable personal shoppers can provide gift suggestions for any occasion. Please call 1 844 KING BABY (546-4222) FREE Monday through Friday, between 9am and 5:30pm PST, or email PERSONALSHOPPER@KINGBABYSTUDIO.COM.
New Customers
Register by clicking HERE to create an account with King Baby for the following benefits:
Receive previews of the latest collections and news available only to email subscribers
Faster checkout
View online order history
Subscribe to our emailing list
Receive exclusive coupons and special offers directly to your inbox.
Join our mailing list
